mallcom.com 2018-02-26

# Mallcom.com

| 

### Data Security

MALLcom is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online.

### Company Commitment to Privacy

We believe strongly in respecting your privacy. However, we also reserve the right to change our privacy policy in order to adapt to new situations. Our commitment is to inform users how we intend to use any information we request before it is collected (so you can opt in), and to respect your wishes to opt out.

MALLcom's website contains links to other websites and is not responsible for privacy practices of those websites. MALLcom encourages users to learn about the privacy practices of those websites.

### Privacy Statement

Protecting your privacy is important to Affiliate Tracking Network (Mallcom). We hope the following policy will help you understand how Mallcom collects, uses, and safeguards the personal information you provide on our website. 

### Information Collection

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously. We don't collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to anything personally identifiable. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information. Like many other commercial websites, the Mallcom website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. This cookie information is intended to determine repeat visit statistics. This information is not shared or otherwise used. In some of our advertising on other web sites, we use a device called a "click-through URL." When you click on one of these URLs, you pass through our system before arriving at a page on our site that is your true destination. Mallcom uses click-throughs to determine the level of interest in particular topics and to measure the effectiveness of our advertising. We do not share this data, and we make no attempt to match click-throughs to particular email addresses. 

### Opting Out

Although most customers tell us they appreciate receiving our mailings, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue mailings from us by simply replying to the email and informing us of your preferences. With the exception of support case correspondence, which is customer initiated, all of our email messages clearly explain how you can easily opt out and stop receiving such messages from us. 

### Data Security

Mallcom is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online.

### Company Commitment to Privacy

We believe strongly in respecting your privacy. However, we also reserve the right to change our privacy policy in order to adapt to new situations. Our commitment is to inform users how we intend to use any information we request before it is collected (so you can opt in), and to respect your wishes to opt out.

Mallcom's website contains links to other websites and is not responsible for privacy practices of those websites. Mallcom encourages users to learn about the privacy practices of those websites. 

|
